And how are you this morning, Danny?
Well, I didn't sleep very well...
...last night, Alan.
I had nightmares.
Nightmares.
I dreamed I ate a 5-pound marshmallow.
A 5-pound marshmallow?
Yeah. And when I woke up,
my pillow was gone.
Pillow was gone.
Pillow.
Pillow. Pillow.
- Alan?
- Yeah?
You're starting to scare the crap
out of me.
Oh, this? This is just a new hobby.
Charlie, say hello to Danny O'Day.
How do you do, Charlie?
That's not a hobby, that's a cry for help.
Oh, come on, Charlie, play along.
So, Charlie, how did you sleep last night?
With a woman, Alan.
Something you need to do
before this gets out of hand.
Oh.
He's got a stick where I've got your hand.
Did you ask him
if he wants to go to the movies?
- No.
- Why not?
Because he's a ticking time bomb...
...and we don't wanna in the car with him
when he goes off.
Come on, he's breaking my heart.
Staying home all alone on a Friday night.
Don't worry.
You know how they say
you can be alone but not lonely?
- Yeah.
- Well, Alan's kind of the opposite.
He's always lonely, but he's never alone.
He's going through a tough time.
Your brother should be surrounded
by friends and family.
My brother should be surrounded
by a SWAT team.
Please? For me?
Chelsea, we agreed
that you only get one of those a month.
Are you sure
you wanna waste it on, Alan?
Thanks for letting me tag along with you.
This is really sweet.
We're thrilled you could join us.
Right, Charlie?
Yippee skippy.
- So have we picked a movie yet?
- Nope.
Would you like to see
La Poubelle et le Fromage at the Nuart?
Would I?
Who you calling wood-eye, big ears?
Now, Danny, watch your mouth.
Why? Yours is the one that's moving.
Yippee skippy.
Hah. If she goes back to him
after what he's done...
...I will never forgive her.
She loves him.
What choice does she have?
She can return to her husband,
the cheese maker.
Listen, I'm gonna hit the head.
Let me know
if any kind of a plot ever kicks in.
He's not coming back is he?
They sell beer in the lobby?
- Yes.
- No.
You're up early for a Saturday morning.
Hence, the cock-a-doodle-doo.
Chelsea? It's 7:30.
We gotta get a move on.
Oh, God, that's right. I forgot.
Give me a few minutes to get dressed.
No problem. I'll wait for you downstairs.
- What's going on?
- Your brother and I are going to the market.
Since when?
We made plans last night.
Last night when?
In the movie theater,
while you were in the lobby drinking.
Well, I wasn't gonna go sit in the car
with that scary dummy.
I like mustard...
...and pickles...
...and ketchup and mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise.
You and me need to talk.
How do you do, Charlie?
Get that ugly thing out of my face.
That's what she said.
Oh, Danny. Danny, you're horrible. Heh.
My hand to God, Alan...
...I will wrap that dummy with meat
and throw him in the ocean.
Don't forget the mayonnaise.
Ow.
I'm okay.
Why are you taking Chelsea
to that farmer's thing?
- Is there a problem?
- Yeah. You're ruining my Saturday.
- I'm sorry, did you have plans for the day?
- Damn right, I had plans.
First, I was gonna have sex with Chelsea.
And then...
Well, then I was gonna go back to sleep.
You can still go back to sleep.
Yeah, but without sex,
it's a restless sleep.
- Fine, fine. I'll just go by myself.
- No, no.
If you go without her now,
then I'm the bad guy.
So, what do you want me to do?
In the future, I want you
to be more sensitive and considerate...
...to other peoples needs.
Okay.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna join Chelsea in the shower...
...and try to knock out a quick one.
Oh, Danny.
Sometimes he can be such a pig.
Well, you know what happens to pigs.
They get slaught-
Danny, don't say it. Don't even think it.
- Ered.
What are you looking at?
JAKE: Nothing.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing here?
Thought you were with your mom and Herb.
I was supposed to...
...but Mom's got those
pregnancy hormones going.
What did you do?
One little fat joke.
Took it badly, eh?
Well, here I am.
Where's Dad?
He went out with Chelsea.
- You mean like a date?
- No. No, not a date.
Good, because that'd be weird.
Yeah.
I saw something like that
on Jerry Springer once.
Two brothers, one girl. It got ugly.
I'm sure it did.
So, what's Dad's dummy doing here?
It pissed off his mother.
Oh.
Hey, I did that too.
Okay. Please take this kettle corn away
from me.
I can feel it going right to my behind.
Oh, stop it.
I wish my tush was as small as yours.
Okay, first of all,
you have a perfect heinie.
Secondly, if you're worried about firmness,
the secret is isometric glute crunches.
- Really?
- You can do them anywhere, any time.
I'm doing them right now. See?
Mailbox open, mailbox closed.
Come on, try it with me.
- Mailbox open, mailbox closed.
Mailbox open, mailbox-
You know, just once I'd like to walk
in this room and not be freaked out.
Alan was just showing me
his butt exercises.
Have him show you the one where he sticks
his head up there. My favorite.
Stop it.
Now, go away, were making dinner.
- It's kind of like a Kegel exercise, isn't it?
- Uh- Exactly.
Except with tush not the hoo-ha.
What up, homes?
What are you doing?
Enjoying the sunset, waiting on dinner.
You're staying for dinner?
I wasn't gonna, but your lovely fiancée
and her new gal pal insisted.
Yeah, I gotta put a stop to that.
What, are you nuts?
This is a perfect setup for you.
- How do you figure?
- Do you like to go shopping?
- No.
- Zippy does.
Do you like to watch chick flicks?
- No.
- Zippy does.
Do you like to talk for hours
about your feelings?
- No.
- Zippy do.
Oh, right.
He digs the trench, you lay the pipe.
How could I not see this?
Alan's not the competition,
he's her gay friend.
There you go. Your life is perfect.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Now, be an angel and get me another beer.
- Absolutely.
Jiminy, I'm drunk.
Oh, I hate to do this to you.
But using the existing S
in the top row...
...with R-E before it,
and I-Z-I-N-G after it...
...hitting two triple-word scores
and it's a bingo.
"Resizing," 120 points.
Oh, my God,
you play for blood, don't you?
Let me tell you something.
When it comes to Scrabble,
nice guys finish with a rack full of tiles.
What do you mean it's not a word?
It's not a word. Try again.
CHARLIE:
Hmm.
Charlie, horny.
- Another glass of wine?
- I would love one.
Now?
But Alan and I are playing Scrabble.
Well, I'm playing Scrabble.
I don't know what she's doing.
I'm improving is what I'm doing.
I want a rematch.
Good night, Alan.
But I just poured wine.
Oh, thanks.
And thanks for being such a good friend
to Chelsea.
I like her and we've got a lot in common.
Yeah, whatever. Just keep it up.
And I'll try to do the same.
Kind of ruin the night.
He's using you.
I know. What am I gonna do?
You could kill him.
Now, Danny, I could never do that.
Don't worry, Alan.
I can do it for you.
- Morning.
Morning.
- Hope you're hungry, I made pancakes.
- Oh, I'm starving. Can I help?
Sure. Slice up some bananas
and warm up the syrup.
- I'm on it.
- Sleep well?
Yeah. I mean, when your brother
finally let me go to sleep.
- Can I tell you a little secret?
- Sure.
- He's the best lover I've ever had.
- Oh, isn't that nice.
Yeah, it's great. But sometimes
he doesn't know when to quit.
Have you tried pepper spray?
No. But every once in a while,
I actually have to give him a little smack...
...on the top of his head.
Yeah, I have the same problem
with Jake when he eats spaghetti.
Well, obviously, not the same problem.
Jake's head is usually over here.
Don't get me wrong, I'm not complaining,
but it can be exhausting.
I can imagine.
Have you given Charlie enough attaboys?
- Attaboys?
- You know, like when you're training a dog.
If you don't give them hugs and a treat,
they're gonna chew up your rug.
I mean, not your rug.
Hey, how are those bananas coming?
- Morning.
- Morning. How'd you sleep?
Good.
When you finally let me.
Hush.
Alan's making pancakes.
- Can I pour you some coffee?
- I would love that.
Good morning, Mrs. Butterworth.
Oh. Lakers-Spurs today.
You promised we'd go
to the van Gogh exhibit.
- I did?
- Yes.
Wow, I don't remember that.
You gotta quit hitting me
on the head so much.
I've heard that exhibit is supposed
to be terrific. I've been dying to see it.
Really? Then why don't we all go.
I can't.
I promised Jake we'd do something.
Bring him along.
What 14-year-old boy
doesn't love a fine-art museum?
That's a great idea,
you and Jake come with us.
- Well, if you don't think we'd be intruding.
- No, not at all.
Okay, great. Heh-heh-heh.
Save me some pancakes.
I'm gonna shower and get ready.
Hurry. I wanna get to the museum
before it's too crowded.
Now, here's the deal.
You're gonna go to the museum
without me.
- Why?
- I am about to get an acute case...
...of intestinal distress.
- What?
- You know, the flapjack two-step.
- There's nothing wrong with my pancakes.
- No, they're delightful.
But Lakers are playing the Spurs,
I'm not gonna miss it.
So what, so you're gonna use me
to entertain your fiancée...
...while you stay home
and watch a basketball game?
Good, we're on the same page.
Did you ever stop to think
maybe I've got plans of my own?
That I've got a life,
that I'm not always at your beck and call.
No.
You know, Berta, I thought when Alan
moved in here, I was being punished.
You and me both.
But come to find out, it was a blessing.
With him in my life, I think I can actually
make my relationship with Chelsea work.
So you're gonna go through
with this marriage?
Absolutely.
I'm ready for the whole shebang.
Kids too?
Well, it's certainly in the cards.
Of course, I'd have to talk it over
with Chelsea and Alan first.
Wow, marriage and kids.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
What can I say, Berta?
He completes me.
One second.
- Ha. He's hilarious.
- Who?
Your brother. I-O-I.
All right.
Let me just tell him we'll talk tomorrow.
He is out of control.
- What now?
- Hang on.
"Don't let him chew up the rug."
- What does that mean?
- Nothing.
Why would I chew up a rug?
Not a rug, my- Never mind.
Okay, where were we?
We just about-
I'm sure he just wants to say good night.
I'm sorry.
Let me just make sure he's okay.
Is he okay?
- Yeah.
- Good, good.
- Hey, I'm thirsty. Are you thirsty?
- No.
- Be right back.
- Hurry.
Don't worry.
This won't take but a minute.
Oh, Charlie, your penis
is no match for my technology.
Okay, I know what you're doing,
now quit it.
What I'm doing? Whatever do you mean?
You're text-blocking me.
Hey, I can't help it
if Chelsea finds me witty and urbane.
Keep it up and she's gonna find you
bloody and homeless.
You don't scare me, Charlie.
You need me
to keep Chelsea off your back.
That may be true, but I don't need him.
Wait, wait. Just let him go, Charlie.
- This is just between you and me.
- Not anymore.
Don't you dare hurt him.
Well, now, that's entirely up to you.
His tiny, wooden head is in your hands.
Charlie?
Danny!
Just let him go now.
- Charlie?
What the hell are you doing?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
That's no way for a grown man to behave.
CHARLIE:
He started it.
I don't care who started it.
You're the older brother,
you set the example.
CHARLIE:
Really? Then maybe I should move out.
Boy, they're really going at it.
Yeah, I'm glad we never fight.
Me too, Danny.
Because you don't ever wanna
make me angry.
I-I-I know, Danny.
Seriously.